In this video, we're going to talk about
本节视频将探讨应用中一些已损坏的功能
We've done a great job so far of setting up Webpack.
到目前为止 我们在设置 webpack 方面做得很棒
But along the way,
但于此同时
we've actually broken a lot of
实际上 我们一开始就已经破坏了应用的功能
So we're going to take a look at all the things that
所以现在就要研究一下所有不能正常工作的功能
aren't working and then we'll start talking about how to fix them.
看看如何修复
Let's take stock of our app.
先评估一下应用
What's working, what isn't,
看看哪些能运行 哪些不能运行
let's figure it all out.
找出所有不能运行的功能
So first, our JavaScript event code isn't running.
首先 JavaScript 事件代码没有运行
We can see that if we go to our app and we try to type something into the form field.
如果打开应用 尝试在表单中输入一些内容 可以看到
None of that custom JavaScript that we wrote is actually happening.
我们编写的自定义 JavaScript 都没有运行
So we'll need to fix that and suss out why it's not working.
所以我们需要修复该问题 找出不能正常运行的原因
The next thing that's not working about our app is the Express Server.
下一个问题是关于 Express 服务器
We've done a lot of Webpack config that's actually
我们做了很多的 webpack 设置
messed up the Express Server that we had working at the beginning.
而这弄乱了一开始设置好的 Express 服务器
So we'll need to reset that.
需要重新设置
It's important that we reset our Express Server because
重置 Express 服务器很重要
our production build that we also haven't set up
因为我们尚未设置的生产构建
yet is going to rely on our Express Server.
需要依赖 Express 服务器
Let's dive into why our JavaScript code isn't working.
深入探索一下 为什么 JavaScript 代码不能正常工作
Webpack tries to keep the global scope really
webpack 会尝试保持全局作用域的 "干净"
clean and you've probably come across the concept of
课程学到现在 你应该已经接触过作用域的概念
heard that it is a good thing to keep the global scope clean.
很可能听说过 保持全局作用域的干净是一件好事
But what that means is that Webpack puts all of our code
但是这意味着 webpack 会将所有代码放入
into encapsulated little libraries and that can be a great thing,
封装好的小库中 这可能是一件好事
it is a great thing.
确实是一件好事
But it can also mean that we have some problems and
但是这同样意味着会有一些问题
those problems are actually what are breaking our code right now.
而这些问题正是现在破坏我们代码的原因
If you look under the hood of what Webpack is actually doing,
如果你了解 webpack 的运行原理
Webpack uses IIFE's to separate all of
webpack 使用的是 IIFE 来分离所有代码
our code and keep it neatly organized into its own little chunks.
将其整齐地组织成自己的小代码块
Now, that is what IIFE's are for and if you haven't come across them,
这正是 IIFE 的用法 如果你还没有接触过这个概念
we're going to get a lot more practice with them in just a second.
稍后会有一些 IIFE 练习来帮助你理解
But for now, all we need to know is that these little chunks of code can't always
但是现在 我们只需要知道 这些小代码块不能
talk to each other and that not being able
一直相互交流 而它们不能相互交流
to talk to each other is what is breaking our event code.
就是破坏事件代码的原因
Let's take a look at a bit more of the JavaScript scope setup.
再深入讨论一下 JavaScript 的作用域设置
In order to understand more what's going wrong with our JavaScript,
要理解我们代码现在的问题
we need to have a good understanding of scope.
需要很好地理解作用域的概念
Now, Webpack is dealing with a lot of JavaScript so it
现在 webpack 处理大量的 JavaScript 代码
encapsulates each chunk of JavaScript into a scope layer.
将每个封装好的代码块放入一个作用域层
Now, you can imagine that if all of
你可以想象 我们的 JavaScript 代码 特别是对于大型应用来说
we could have thousands of lines of JavaScript,
可能会有成千上万行代码
and if Webpack didn't encapsulate everything,
如果 webpack 不进行任何封装
we would end up with just all of our stuff thrown
最终所有代码都会被扔到
into one huge global scope and we would have to make sure
一个巨大的全局作用域中 我们必须确保
that variable names didn't conflict with other variable names
变量名不会产生冲突
and it would just be chaos like you see here.
最终会像这里一样 一团乱麻
But with scope, we get
但是利用作用域 我们可以获得
these neatly stacked scope layers and the IIFF's are what allow Webpack to do that.
这些整齐堆叠的作用域层 是 webpack 用 IIFE 完成的
Now, one problem with that is that sometimes
现在 这里有一个问题是
we lose communication between these two scope layers.
我们失去了两个层级之间的交流
The browser events like our form submit are happening on the global level but our code,
浏览器事件 (比如表单提交) 发生在全局层
the custom JavaScript that we wrote is happening on the function level
但是我们编写的自定义 JavaScript 发生在函数层
and our problem is that we lack the communication between these two layers.
我们的问题就是缺乏这两层之间的交流
So what we need to do is come up with a fix that allows our functions to
所以需要提供一种修复方案
be callable by the global scope or when a browser event happens.
使函数可以在全局作用域内或者浏览器事件发生时被调用
So now, we're going to change and let you get some time
现在 我们先转移焦点 给你一些时间理解 IIFE
with IIFE's because there are fantastic JavaScript strategy to know.
因为这是一种非常出色、需要了解的 JavaScript 策略
But when we come back,
再次回来时
we're going to talk about the fix for our Webpack JavaScript.
我们就要讨论如何修改 webpack JavaScript 来修复问题了。最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6